const data = [
 

  {
    question: "What does EDA stands for?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Extensive Data Analysis",
      "Exploratory Data Analytics",
      "Examplary Data  Analysis",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Exploratory Data Analysis",
  },
  {
    question: " What is technique used for Feature Selection.?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Dimensionality reduction analysis", "Exploration", "None of the options"],
    correctAnswer: "Principal component analysis",
  },

  {
    question: "What is the name of the functions in Support Vector Mahcine (SVM) which takes a low dimentional input space and transform to a higher dimensional space.?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Hyperplane",
      "Support Vector",
      "Vector",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kernels",
  },

  {
    question: "In time series the mostly widely used mathematical technique to calculate the trend is  ?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Semi average",
      "Moving average",
      "Free hand curve",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Least squares",
  },

  



  {
    question: "In Time series the seasonal variations are ?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Sudden variation",
      "Long term variation",
      "No varitation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Short term variation",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the components of time series?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Cyclic variation",
      "Trend",
      "Seasonal variation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All the options",
  },

  {
    question: " If a Time series data changes at a constant increase/decrease then ",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "A linear fit to the logarithms data gives a perfect fit",
      "A nonlinear is required to fit and gives the perfect fit",
      "A well-fitted trend line cannot be obtained",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A linear line fitted to the data gives a perfect fit",
  },
{
  question: "In Time series if a pattern of variation that occurs every year is known as ?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Cyclical variation",
      "Trend",
      "Cyclic variation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Seasonal variation",
  },

  {
    question: "Times series graphs are mostly ?",
      incorrectAnswers: [
        "Trend",
        "Box plot",
        "Line graph",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Histogram",
    },
    {
      question: " A bookstore company delaying the manufaction of books for some weeks is an example of ?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
          "Cyclic trend",
          "Secular trend",
          "Seasonal trend",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Irregular trend",
      },

      {
        question: "Choose one of the cross validation techniques which is better suited for time series data ?",
          incorrectAnswers: [
            "Stratified shuffle split cross validation",
            "Leave one out cross validation",
            "k-fold cross validation",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Forward chaining cross validation",
        },

        {
          question: "Scatter plots were drawn during correlation to check assumptions of ?",
            incorrectAnswers: [
              "Unbiasness",
              "Multicollinearity",
              "Homoscedasticity",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Linearity",
          },

          {
            question: "The trend in a time series which is over a long term appears as ?",
              incorrectAnswers: [
                "Straight-line",
                "Downward",
                "Upward",
              ],
              correctAnswer: "Parabolic curve or Third Degree Curve",
            },

            {
              question: "We call a trend to be a better fitted trend if the sum of squares of residuals is :?",
                incorrectAnswers: [
                  "Maximum",
                  "Negative",
                  "Positive",
                ],
                correctAnswer: "Minimum",
              },

              {
                question: " An accidental situation or a mal function in a company is an example of?",
                  incorrectAnswers: [
                    "Seasonal trend",
                    "Cyclical variations",
                    "Seasonal movements",
                  ],
                  correctAnswer: "Irregular variations",
                },
      
];

export default data;
